<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Technically Lewb</title>
    <link>https://yourwebsite.com/technically-lewb</link>
    <description>Weekly fun and informative takes on the latest in tech and gaming, from GTA leaks to wild new gadgets.</description>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2025 12:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <managingEditor>lewis@yourdomain.com</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>lewis@yourdomain.com</webMaster>

    <item>
      <title>Week 1: GTA Leaks, CoD Goes Hollywood, and a VR Suit That Makes You Sweat</title>
      <link>https://yourwebsite.com/technically-lewb/week1</link>
      <guid>https://yourwebsite.com/technically-lewb/week1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[
        <h2>1. GTA 6 Leaks... Again?</h2>
        <p>Just when Rockstar thought they plugged the leaks, another batch of <em>alleged</em> screenshots popped up online this week—this time showing off a revamped Vice City nightlife and new vehicle customisation UI. Rockstar, as usual, is silent—but insiders are whispering about a <strong>holiday 2025 trailer drop</strong>. Buckle up, it's happening.</p>

        <h2>2. Call of Duty: Black Ops Gulf War – Full Reveal Incoming</h2>
        <p>The <em>worst-kept secret</em> in gaming might finally get its moment: Treyarch’s next entry is rumoured to be revealed at <strong>Summer Game Fest in June</strong>, with a <strong>campaign set in the 1990s Gulf War</strong> and <strong>open-world-style missions</strong>. Leaked concept art shows desert ops, stealth tech, and—yes—an actual zipline mechanic. It’s giving <em>Modern Warfare 2019</em> vibes, and we’re here for it.</p>

        <h2>3. Tech Spotlight: The VR Suit That Makes You Sweat (Literally)</h2>
        <p>A startup called OWO has created a haptic feedback suit that not only lets you <em>feel</em> in-game hits—but adjusts <strong>temperature and resistance</strong>, so yes, you can feel heat, wind, and simulated punches. It's being demoed with horror games, because of course it is. Who needs peaceful gaming when you can feel every monster’s breath on your neck?</p>

        <h2>4. Bonus Bytes:</h2>
        <ul>
          <li><strong>Apple’s AI assistant</strong> rumors are heating up again—expect an announcement at WWDC in June. Siri might finally grow up.</li>
          <li><strong>Tesla’s “Autopark Anywhere” update</strong> lets your car parallel park with zero human input... or judgment.</li>
          <li><strong>Steam Spring Sale</strong> just ended, but people are still playing <em>Palworld</em> like it’s 2023. The bird guns are back, baby.</li>
        </ul>

        <p><strong>Stay Technically Lewb.</strong></p>
      ]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
